<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BluetoothK&amp;M</string>
    <string name="LMB">Left Click</string>
    <string name="RMB">Right Click</string>
    <string name="select_device_str">Select your device:</string>
    <string name="start">START</string>
    <string name="exit">EXIT</string>
    <string name="help">HELP</string>
    <string name="getting_started_str">1. Getting Started</string>
    <string name="how_to_use_str">2. How to use</string>
    <string name="create_macros_str">3. Create Macros</string>
    <string name="keycodes_str">4. Macros and Key Codes</string>
    <string name="sensors_str">5. Sensors</string>
    <string name="troubleshooting_str">6. Troubleshooting</string>


    <string name="settings">SETTINGS</string>
    <string name="manage_macros_str">Manage your macros:</string>
    <string name="add_str">Add a new macro</string>
    <string name="name_str">Name :</string>
    <string name="add_key_str">Add a key</string>
    <string name="keys_str">Keys :</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="sensitivity">Sensitivity:</string>
    <string name="m_sensitivity">Mouse Sensitivity:</string>
    <string name="s_sensitivity">Scroll Sensitivity:</string>
    <string name="help_1"> FIRST STEPS: \n
        \t First, you need to set up a bluetooth server on your computer.\n
        To do this, you need to download it from this link:\n
        https://mega.nz/#!fQhGAKqJ!qRF2xtOyVWNDYooXYwsKrnC-qZVVdC_MdY_c81Qou3Y\n\n
        Once downloaded, you have to open a command prompt and run the BluetoothServer.jar file
        by writing the command:\n
        \"java -jar BluetoothServer.jar\"\n
        This will start the server on your computer so the android device can be connected.\n
        After this, you have to pair your android device with your computer using bluetooth, so your
        computer will become visible in the device selection screen of this App.\n
        Once the device has been successfully paired, you just have to select it from the screen and
        you\'re ready to go!
    </string>
    <string name = "help_2">USING THE MOUSE:\n
        \t Once connected, you will see a central pannel that can be used to move the cursor, in the
        same way that you would do with a laptop touchpad.\n
        The touchpad can detect click and double-click motion, but you can also use the two mouse
        buttons on the top.\n
        To use the keyboard, click the big button at the bottom of the screen.\n
        To switch between keyboard and keyboard macros, swipe the bottom portion of the screen to
        the left or right.\n
        You can also change the mouse sensitivity with the two seekbars below the touchpad.
    </string>
    <string name = "help_3">EDITING YOUR MACROS:\n
        \t You can create, modify or delete personalized key combinations or "keyboard macros".\n
        To do this, you cave to select the "Settings" option at the main menu, and you will be
        presented with a grid of buttons, each one representing a macro.\n
        To create a new macro, press the "+" button at the top of the screen.\n
        To modify or delete an existing macro, press and hold the macro you want to modify.
    </string>

    <string name = "help_4">MACRO CODES: \n
        \t If you tried to create or modify a macro, you would already have noticed that they use
        specific keywords to represent the desired keys to press, like "KEYCODE_CTRL_LEFT". These
        codenames represent each of the keys that the macro will press, and must be separated by a
        slash "/". You can see the full list of Key Codes in this page:\n
        https://developer.android.com/reference/android/view/KeyEvent.html#Constants
    </string>

    <string name = "help_5">USING THE SENSORS: \n
        \t You can use your motion sensors to move the cursor in the screen!\n
        To do this, you simply have to toggle the desired motion mode using the 2 toggle buttons:
        "accel" or "gyro".\n\n
        -accel lets you use your phone as a mouse, by sliding it over a flat surface\n
        -gyro lets you move the mouse by tilting your phone in different directions
    </string>

    <string name = "help_6">IF YOU CANT START THE SERVER ON LINUX: \n\n
    Install the following packages:\n
    libbluetooth\n
    libbluetooth3\n
    libbluetooth-dev\n\n


    Open a terminal and run:\n
    sudo nano /etc/systemd/system/bluetooth.target.wants/bluetooth.service\n

    then change the line:\n

    ExecStart=/usr/lib/bluetooth/bluetoothd\n

    to:\n

    ExecStart=/usr/lib/bluetooth/bluetoothd -C\n

    then reload the bluetooth daemon:\n

    sudo systemctl daemon-reload\n

    sudo systemctl restart bluetooth\n\n

    If the problem persists, try running the server in super user (sudo) mode.
    </string>

</resources>
